<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Thync / Vibe Sessions</title>
    <description>Welcome to the Thync Vibe Sessions.</description>
    <link>http://yourdomain.com/thync/welcome//</link>
    <atom:link href="http://yourdomain.com/thync/welcome//feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2015 15:15:35 -0700</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2015 15:15:35 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Wells Fargo Maker Lab</title>
        <description>&lt;p class=&quot;event-logo&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;assets/vibesessions.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;40%&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;welcome&quot;&gt;Welcome.&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’d like to personally welcome you to the Thync Immersion. This is an environment for learning and experimentation, designed for building coherence and clarity internally. We seek to learn the basic parameters of what makes a great guided Vibe experience for your target users segments.  Our aim as a team is to discover, test, validate, and polish studio-quality Welcome Vibes and Premium Vibes that dramatically  enhance the onboarding process and overall user experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During our time together, we will be focusing on two activities:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Improving the Welcome Vibes experience for Calm and Energy by 10x&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Developing and testing “moonshot” Premium Vibe tracks for two user segments: athletes and meditators.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;the-essentials&quot;&gt;The Essentials&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;what&quot;&gt;What&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;24+ real and potential customers, the Thync team, sound designers and the Metapattern team coming together to learn the mindsets, tactics and strategies needed to build and run effective sprints.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are guided by two open inquiries:
How might we dramatically improve (10x) the Calm and Energy Welcome Vibes through thoughtful sound design and guided narration?
How might we explore and tell the story of Premium Vibes and the Vibe Marketplace?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Two teams test against a set of distinct customer archetypes to prototype and measure the impact of different styles of guided Vibes per our framework.  In total, 24 customers selected from the known customer segments will be tested during the Immersion as qualitative feedback. Vibes go ‘head-to-head’ until a clear set of characteristics emerge as preferred by each segment.  At the end of day one, findings are synthesized and refined and tested again on day two, until we reach a polished product that are ready for market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The third ‘moonshot’ team focuses on a Premium Vibes track to measure the appeal and impact of being guided by a celebrity voice.  This team gathers insights and tests the idea of a content marketplace with existing Thync users to better understand the long-term potential.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;when&quot;&gt;When&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;September 23rd - 24th, 2015 / 10:00am - 6:30p (both days) &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;where&quot;&gt;Where&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;140 W Main St. 
Los Gatos, CA 95030
United States&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.google.com/maps/embed?pb=!1m18!1m12!1m3!1d3177.0614896613765!2d-121.9829965!3d37.22251519999999!2m3!1f0!2f0!3f0!3m2!1i1024!2i768!4f13.1!3m3!1m2!1s0x808e35fae0c69ed5%3A0x10a77a40a783e492!2s140+W+Main+St%2C+Los+Gatos%2C+CA+95030!5e0!3m2!1sen!2sus!4v1442336743879&quot; width=&quot;800&quot; height=&quot;450&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; style=&quot;border:0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;who&quot;&gt;Who&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Δ / Team: Carson Linforth Bowley (principal); Mikyö Clark (principal); Ting Kelly (co-facilitator); Chad Owen (producer)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;preparation&quot;&gt;Preparation&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;how-can-i-be-most-prepared-for-this&quot;&gt;How can I be most prepared for this?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Try to get at least 8 hours of sleep the night before.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Set up an email auto-responder so you can be fully present.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;Listen to &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.radiolab.org/story/9-volt-nirvana/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;this RadioLab podcast&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;Download and try &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.headspace.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Headspace&lt;/a&gt; (a free meditation app)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-should-i-bring-the-day-of&quot;&gt;What should I bring the day of?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Yourself&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A pair of headphones&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A notepad&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Any special needs you may have&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Your curiosity and open mind&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-should-i-expect&quot;&gt;What should I expect?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The immersion process is all about speed, collaboration and experience. Starting with lo-fi materials, often a whiteboard or paper &amp;amp; pen, we can collaboratively prototype, test and evolve many concepts. Have an idea? Don’t talk about it, build and test it. With so much speed, communication and energy, the work begins to feel something like a sport. We call it “athletic design”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over the course of the two days, we will go through 4 complete prototyping cycles (concept &amp;gt; prototype &amp;gt; test &amp;gt; iterate).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’ve found that ideas are important, but they’re relatively weak compared to direct experience. So our work focuses on bringing ideas to life as soon as possible. “Experience is the medium, “ after all. Over the course of our two day sprint, we’ll experiment with several facets of the Vibe audio experience, from the narrator’s script and delivery to the inclusion of music and sonic branding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Expect to hustle, play and listen. Expect to share your wild ideas, and hear others. Expect to work hard and have a great time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;days&quot;&gt;Days&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Day 1: Collective visioning and producing low-fidelity vibe prototypes based on real user feedback&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Day 2: Producing and refining high-fidelity prototypes based on real user feedback&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;teams&quot;&gt;Teams&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Calm (Dan, Edwin, Eve, Doug)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Energy (Jonathan (Boston), Kerrigan, Liz, Rafal)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Premium (Chris M, Caroline, Jamie (Boston), Sumon (Boston))&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-are-the-desired-outcomes&quot;&gt;What are the desired outcomes?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We believe that bringing sound to Vibes has the power to dramatically improve Thync’s user experience. For new users, voice can bring clarity and comfort to their first Vibes. For more advanced users, voice guidance and music have enormous potential to make Vibes into rich, interactive experience. In essence, our work is to engage the Mind and much as the device engages the Brain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond improving the baseline Vibe experience, sound design may open up a new market for Thync: Premium Vibes. From athletes to executives to gurus, we believe Thync can connect thought leaders to their audiences in a revolutionarily personal way. And through these thought leaders, Thync can reach a wide audience quickly and deeply.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;contact-information&quot;&gt;Contact Information&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have have any questions or emergencies, please don’t hesitate to contact our producer, Chad Owen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chad Owen, Producer&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;cell&lt;/strong&gt; 512.589.6056 / &lt;strong&gt;email&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:chad@metapattern.is&quot;&gt;chad@metapattern.is&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;resources&quot;&gt;Resources&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;required-listening&quot;&gt;Required Listening&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.radiolab.org/story/9-volt-nirvana/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;9-Volt Nirvana (Radiolab)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.headspace.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Headspace&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2015 04:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/thync/welcome//jekyll/update/2015/07/13/Welcome.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/thync/welcome//jekyll/update/2015/07/13/Welcome.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
